=== GroundWork ===
Contributors: chrisdnilsson@gmail.com
Tags: library, resource management, staff development, icafe
Requires at least: 3.0
Tested up to: 3.5.1
Stable tag: 1.0.1
License: GPLv2 or later
License URI: http://www.gnu.org/licenses/gpl-2.0.html
GroundWork creates beautiful functional organization of resource materials for Professional Development or Training.
== Description ==
GroundWork is a plugin designed to create beautiful functional resource libraries for Professional Development delivery.
With a few steps you can create highly organized resource libraries designed to allow users to easily find the support documents, videos, or links they need. 
If you are tired of managing hundreds of how-to guides that users can't find then GroundWork is for you. Primarily designed to be used by Public Education Staff Development Departments but any department responsible for organizational training can benefit from GroundWork.
Visit a live and growing GroundWork library in the [iCafe Resource library] [icafe]
**The Promethean book is currently the most developed on the site.** 
Features:
*  Simple Resource Tile Creation
*  Organize Resources into Books>Chapters>Sections>Tiles
*  Drag and Drop Reordering

[icafe]: http://icafe.lcisd.org/resources "iCafe"

== Installation ==

1. Upload `GroundWork` folder to the `/wp-content/plugins/` directory
1. Activate the plugin through the 'Plugins' menu in WordPress
1. Watch the included tutorial on the main plugin dashboard menu
1. Create some content
1. Place the shortcode '[groundwork]' on a page
1. Enjoy your library!

== Frequently asked questions ==

= How do I get started? =

Activate the plugin and click on GroundWork from the side menu.

= How are resources organized? =

The concept of a bookshelf is used. You create books which can contain Chapters which can contain Sections.

= Where to I put the resources? =

Resource Tiles can be added to any Chapter or Section.

= What are "Resource Tiles" =

Resource should be very narrow in their focus. A "Tile" is a simple container that holds related Text, Video, or Links together in a organizational and visual way.

= Can I reuse a Tile? =

As many times as you like!

= How do I change the order of my "Bookshelf" or chapters, sections, resources? =

Simply Drag and Drop to the correct order or organization...Changes are automatically saved.

= Can I link to a particular Resource Tile to share with a user? =

Yes, just navigate to that tile and copy the URL from the browser.

= My tiles are appearing below the navigation instead of to the right? =

Your template is too narrow. GroundWork requires a full width template with no sidebars or widget areas.

== Screenshots ==

1. Creating a Book

2. Organizing Books, Chapters, Sections

3. Creating a Resource Tile

4. Adding a Tile to a Section

5. Your Bookshelf

6. Easy Organization and Navigation

== Changelog ==

= 1.0.1 =
* Readme.txt changes.
* Fixes to SVN layout to enable screenshots in Wordpress.org repository

= 1.0 =
* First Public Release.

== Upgrade Notice ==


